quarterly.co 2016-04-05

# Privacy Policy | Online Privacy Standards | Quarterly.co

## Quarterly Privacy Policy

Effective as of September 9, 2011 

1: INTRODUCTION 

At Quarterly, Inc., we take the privacy of our Quarterly website members very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how Quarterly, Inc. (“Quarterly,” “we,” our,” or “us”), treats information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with the [http://quarterly.co](http://quarterly.co/) website (the “Quarterly Service” or the “Service”). We provide this Privacy Policy because you have a right to know what information we collect, how it is protected and used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [privacy@quarterly.co](mailto:privacy@quarterly.co) or in writing at: P.O. Box 27397 Los Angeles, CA 90027. 

Online Privacy Standards. We follow the principles supported by the Federal Trade Commission’s Fair Information Practices Principles, currently available at <https://www.ftc.gov/reports/privacy-online-fair-information-practices-electronic-marketplace-federal-trade-commission>. 

What This Policy Covers. This policy covers the ways in which Quarterly treats information, including personally identifiable information, which we obtain when you use our Service. We regard “personally identifiable information” as information that someone can use to identify or contact you in person, such as your real name, telephone number, email address, or physical mailing address. Information that we use internally to identify you as a member in our system is not considered personally identifiable information. Your IP address is not considered personally identifiable information. 

What This Policy Does Not Cover. This policy does not cover the privacy practices of third parties that we do not own or control, such as third-party payment processing services or our partners and advertisers. In addition, we may provide links to other services and on occasion to other sites that may interest you. All of these sites operate independently of Quarterly and they have their own privacy and security practices. For your best on-line experience, we encourage you to review their policies before submitting any personal information to them. 

2: HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION 

**Information You Provide During Account Creation**

Registration Information. During the membership registration process, we require that you provide us with an email address, your real name, and your physical address. As explained below, though you are required to provide payment information during the registration process, Quarterly does not collect, store, or retain payment information for any member. 

Access To Your Personal Information. In general, we make it easy for you to view the personally identifiable information we have collected from you. That information is available at your member account page, where you can add, edit, or delete such personally identifiable information as you see fit. 

**Information We Do Not Collect From Any Users**

Children. As explained further in our Terms of Use (available at http://quarterly.co/terms), you must be 18 years of age or older – or, if you are under the age of majority in your jurisdiction, have the consent of your parent or guardian – to use the Quarterly Service. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information about children. In accordance with Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), Quarterly will never knowingly solicit, nor will we accept, personally identifiable information from users known to be under thirteen (13) years of age. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at [privacy@quarterly.co](mailto:privacy@quarterly.co) or write to our Privacy Officer at the address noted above. 

Social Security Number. We do not require your social security number to use the Quarterly Service or to access any part of our site. Quarterly will never ask for your social security number. 

Payment Information. The Quarterly Service makes it quick and convenient for you to make reoccurring payments to Quarterly using Recurly. See http://recurly.com. Quarterly will not receive any additional personally identifiable information as a result of these transactions. This third-party payment provider operate independently of Quarterly, and we encourage you to fully review the Terms of Use and Privacy Policies at http://recurly.com. Though Quarterly cannot access or view your payment information, Quarterly will delete any such information you may provide to Recurly if you choose to close your Quarterly account. 

**Information We Track**

Log Files. Similar to many websites and internet services, we gather certain anonymous, non-personal information automatically and store it in web server log files. This information includes internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), site entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, and gather aggregate information about our user base as a whole. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or users from which individual user identities have been removed, and therefore does not include your personally identifiable information. We may analyze such data using Google Analytics, or other similar third-party services. 

Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. It can also help us understand how our site visitors click to our site, what pages they view during their visit, and their account and preference information as members of the Service. Similar to many websites, the Quarterly Service may store an encrypted cookie on your computer so we can remember you when you come back without requiring you to log in each time. Cookies also allow us to track and understand the interests of our users to enhance the overall experience on our site. Cookies used by Quarterly do not include your personally identifiable information 

If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your web browser software to disable them. To do so, please refer to the help section of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or disable cookies. Please note that your browser must be configured to accept cookies to use the Quarterly Service. 

3: HOW WE USE INFORMATION 

**To Provide You With Quarterly Services**

We use your information, including personally identifiable information, for the purposes of providing you with the Service, and with any other Quarterly goods or services you may elect to receive. We share your information, including your personally identifiable information, to the minimum extent necessary. For example, if we are shipping physical goods to you, we will share your name and shipping address with our distribution and shipping partners. 

**In Quarterly Communications**

We use emails and/or prominent notifications on our website as our primary means to inform our users of important Service and promotional announcements. 

Service-Related Announcements. When you establish an account at [http://quarterly.co](http://quarterly.co/), we use the email address provided during account creation to deliver important Service-related announcements to you. Examples of Service-related announcements include: email verification during registration, requests for password reset, important security or server maintenance updates, upgrades, and new releases, or policy changes. These Service-related announcements are considered a fundamental part the Quarterly Service, and members cannot opt-out of these email announcements. 

Promotional Announcements. In order to improve the experience for our members, we will send you regular updates from Quarterly from time to time. These communications are enhancements to our service and are entirely optional. We will make it easy for you to unsubscribe from these communications either through the emails themselves or though your account management options page. 

Gift Subscription Program. If you choose to use our referral tool to tell a friend about the Quarterly Service, or about specific content made available through the Service, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site or to view the content you wish to share. We store this information for the purpose of sending this one-time email, and to track the success of our referral program only. Quarterly will not use this email address for any other purpose. 

**On Our Website**

Site Statistics. As noted above, we use information collected from our web log files to calculate and publish anonymous, non-personal, aggregate statistics that we believe our members are interested in viewing. For example, we may track and publish the total number of members who have signed up for a particular special offer. We publish this data in aggregate form only, and this aggregate data does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

**For Internal Reporting and Analysis**

As noted above, we use information gathered from log files and cookies to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site, and to gather aggregate information about our user base as a whole. 

4: HOW WE SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION 

**With Third-Parties**

Sharing, Renting, and Selling Information We Collect. We will neither rent nor sell your personally identifiable information to anyone. Occasionally we share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate information about our members with partners or advertisers, and we may publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website for the interest of our users. This shared or published data does not contain the personally identifiable information of any person. 

Linked Services. In some cases, we allow you to access or link to other web services through our website. For example, we allow users to share content using Facebook and Twitter. We make it easy for you to determine when you are accessing or linking to these other web services through our website. In all of these cases, those sites may choose to collect your personal information as they deem appropriate. As noted above, we are not responsible for or in control of how third parties collect, use, or disclose your information obtained through these linked services. We encourage you to be aware when you are using these third party services and, for your best on-line experience, we encourage you to review their policies before submitting any personal information to them. 

**As Necessary In Certain Legal Circumstances**

Legal Requirements. We reserve the right to disclose your information, including personally identifiable information, when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to (a) comply with any law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce these Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations of these Terms of Service, © detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Quarterly, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 

Acquisition. If Quarterly becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, including bankruptcy, our assets, including member information, may be transferred to a third party. At that time, your member information may become subject to that third party’s privacy policy. Before we transfer your user information, we will notify you either by email or by posting a prominent notice on our site, and we will remind you of your ability to add, edit or delete your personally identifiable information from your account management options page in advance of any such transfer. 

5: HOW WE KEEP INFORMATION SECURE 

Security of Account Information. Your account information is password protected. We will not share your password with anyone. Please do not share your password with anyone, and remember to change your password from time to time, to keep your account information secure. 

Network Security. Our partners employ a variety of commercially standard encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information, including your personal information, unauthorized access. Please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, thus we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Management Procedures. Our partners maintain standard physical and electronic procedural safeguards that limit access to your personally identifiable information to employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who, through the course of standard business activities, need to access your personally identifiable information. 

6: YOUR PERSONAL CHOICES 

Receiving Communications. If you subscribe to any optional promotional communications, you will be able to unsubscribe from these communications through your account management options or through the emails we send you. 

Editing / Deleting Your Account Information. Any member who establishes a Quarterly Service account can view the personally identifiable information we have collected from that member. That information is available at the member’s account page, where members can add, edit, or delete such personally identifiable information as the member sees fit. To completely delete your account and accompanying personal information, or to delete information about you we may have received from a third party in connection with our Gift Subscription Program, please contact us at support@quarterly.co. As noted above, though Quarterly does not store payment information for any users, we are able to delete your payment information from our third-party payment provider at your request. 

7: UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

From time to time, we will review and may make changes to our privacy policy. When we do so, we will notify you either by email or place a prominent notice on our website. The most recent version of our privacy policy is always available from a link on our homepage, and at http://quarterly.co/privacy. 

Top
